So, nobody believed that this was
possible. Nobody thought that you could
crash [music] Bugatti, buy it back, and
nonetheless fix it. Well, that's what
they said.
>> What do you got to say to that? Listen,
man.
>> I think we can rebuild this.
>> You think so?
>> I think we can. [__] him. Let's go.
[__] fix it.
>> 21, [music]
can you do something for me? Can you hit
a little rich [music] flex for me? And
21, can [singing] you do something for
me? Can you talk to the ops next [music]
for me? 21, do your thing. Do your
thing. [music] Do your thing. [singing]
21. Yellow diamonds in the
>> Here it is. And it's in his basketball
court. [laughter] You might have seen
all the videos that Alex has been
filming with the car, which is obviously
not the purpose of the car. diving
board, baseball bats, Jake Paul
reversing into it, Jake Paul pulling up
to the uh boxing event, pushed by it, I
think.
>> Yeah, we were pushing the be on it.
Yeah.
>> Yeah. Now, now all of this comes to a
stop now because [laughter] we've
actually got to repair it. First thing I
think what everyone's going to want to
know is like why why do you buy it back?
>> So, I my first original thought process
was that when am I going to have the
opportunity to buy my second Bugatti
Pier Sport back? you know, like I I
thought that I was just going to crash
it, lose it, and never have it back. But
it's like a sentimental attachment that
I have to the car, and I just didn't
want to not have it anymore. You know, I
could have totally bought another one.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> But I just like this one, you know, and
uh it's also like a big [__] you, you
know? [laughter]
>> Exactly. I think I think it's a Yeah, I
think it makes sense. Well, I have a
sentimental attachment to most of my
cars, but then to buy this back and you
spent how much?
>> I spent $2 million cash.
>> Yeah. You can't you can't finance like a
crash damaged car.
>> You know, it's just not insured, [music]
right?
>> Oh, yeah. Because it because it's
crashed.
>> Yeah, it's crashed. Yeah. I I I can't
insure it because the bank is going to
come. They're going to come inspect it
and be like, "Yeah, we're going to
insure a [__] up battery. [laughter]
Going to do it."
>> So, it's not insured. He has to spend $2
million cash and now we're in this
situation that we can't get parts for.
>> Whoa. That's what you're here for.
[laughter]
>> We originally called Matt Remac when
kind of like the first, oh, we're going
to 3D print the parts. You have 24
hours. He actually hit us up within that
24-hour time span. And then he hit us up
and he's like, "Look, you have my word
that if we can't come to an agreement on
us selling you parts or the car coming
over here, if I have to have one of my
techs there in person while Matt or
whoever is rebuilding the car, so be it.
We just want to make sure we preserve
the Bugatti brand and there's a
technician making sure that things are
being done properly."
>> Yeah.
>> And I took that word and I said, "Okay,
[__] it." He calls us the next day or
two days later and then he basically
said, "Look, there's no way that we can
sell you parts because the carbon tub,
the monog, blah blah blah blah blah,
right? All these other parts, it's a s
it's a safety hazard that these things
are potentially broken because they're
not actually verified that they're
broken yet."
>> Yeah.
>> Uh we can't sell you parts because of
that. So, for that reason,
>> everything's off the table. We're like,
"Well, you you kind of committed
previously and now you're kind of going
back on the word." And that's where
everything went out the window for me.
>> Yeah. That's the the thing that's crazy
is that you buy a car and any other car
you'll be able to buy your own parts
for. But this the fact that they can
refuse to sell your parts. It is crazy.
Like I I think that I think it is wild.
But I'm hoping it doesn't end up being
us versus Bugatti, but it might really
will be like that. That's Yeah, they
desperately want the car back and they
want to protect the brand. I protect the
brand. I think they they don't want us
taking apart the car saying, "Oh, this
is from this car. This is from that
car." And then also, they don't want a
car put back on the road with huge panel
gaps and things wrong and things
rattling because it doesn't look good on
Bugatti. So, I can see why they want it
back, but at the same time, you should
have the right to repair your own car. I
It seems crazy that they would take that
away.
>> I mean, and they gave you a crazy offer
to actually fix [music] it properly, you
know.
>> Yeah. Yeah, we heard about that. So,
originally it was 1.7 million.
Originally just the parts were 1.7
million.
>> And then how much was it that he offered
to take it back?
>> So I think it was 67. [laughter]
>> I think it was 600 $700,000. They were
going to repair the whole entire car,
put a new transmission, new carbon tub,
new mon, but I'm talking about like new
car and stamped by Bugatti that the car
is now good.
>> When he told me that, I was like, why
has he not done it? But then the more
I've thought about it, the more it makes
sense why Alex hasn't done it. Because I
think what they're going to do is take
the car. They're going to take the car
to France. There's no time schedule on
this rebuild. And as soon as this car is
in France in Bugatti, that car, I can
guarantee it is not coming out for at
least a couple of years because all
these cars again are handbuilt. Every
they're not just going to have
headlights on the shelf. They're not
just going to have a bonnet on the
shelf. Everything's going to have to be
made. It's going to be a long, long
time. And they're in control of it. Soon
as that car's gone, you've completely
lost control. Seems crazy, E, but I can
see why you haven't done it. Yeah. They
kept saying, "Oh, we'll pay for the
shipping out of here," which is like
50K, 60K. Yeah.
>> And you don't have to pay us until the
car is fully done. You know, it's it's a
great offer.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yeah. But I'm like, bro, I I feel like
as soon as they come pick up the car and
it's on the plane there, feel like Matt
Rimme is just going to
>> Yeah. I I [laughter] think I I think
that's I think it literally will be the
as soon as they've got that car in the
hand, they're just like, "Stop this guy
hitting the car with a baseball bat and
then that's all we need." So, [laughter]
the first thing I've seen the headlights
are the headlights.
>> I I tried to, you know, get a little bit
ahead of myself. [laughter]
I [__] off, man.
>> So, you managed to get them out.
>> Yeah. Well, I I didn't get them out.
>> There was this Mexican guy that was
cutting the grass and he's like, "Hey,
dude. I I I can help you." [laughter]
I'm like, "All right, take them out."
And he took
like, "Hey, bro. They were so easy to
take out." So, our goal was to get them
to Europe, which is where the guy was
at.
>> Yeah.
>> And then you were going to bring them
back.
>> Yeah. But I was going to send them on
FedEx or UPS. But my worry was one, they
could get lost. Two, they could get even
more damaged. So I'm like, you know
what? It's better if one of my guys go
with a carry-on. Like you need they take
them. Cool. I I get him his tickets.
Normal. When he gets to the terminal to
go get onto the plane, I guess since we
didn't get him first class tickets, they
did not let him put the bags as a
carry-on. He was going to have to send
them under.
>> Yeah.
>> So I'm like, "Oh, dude. It's going to be
It's the same risk. They could get
damaged
>> or lost.
>> Get lost. It's not even worth it. Called
it off. So, the headlights are they're
in the garage. But
>> so, this is a Now, this is going to be
the whole challenge of trying to find
out what we can repair, what we can
make, what and who we can find to make
it. But there there's a lot there.
>> So, we're going to have to build parts
to fix this
>> pretty much. But this guy's rich, so we
can make so much money off [laughter]
this.
>> Like, you know, we're friends now,
right?
>> We're going to make so much money coming
in a private jet today.
>> [laughter]
>> I can't wait.
>> Well, it doesn't look as bad as what I
remember, but a lot of the parts are
going to be used from Volkswagen and
other cars. And you did say that you
wanted to pull this out.
>> Yeah. Well, we could tie it to the BMW
and just yank it out.
>> I think that might be a good start. The
first time we seen this car, we weren't
allowed to touch it at all because it
was technically going through an
insurance claim. But now, cuz Alex owns
it, we can literally just do what we
want to We can do whatever.
>> We can do literally,
>> bro. Smash the windshield. [laughter]
>> No, I can't. I can't.
>> Smash it. Okay, if you if you don't, I'm
going to stand here and I'm going to
jump in it. Smash it. You got to
>> Oh, I I'll happily I [laughter] cannot
do that. Please. Please, dude. We need
to get the windshield out anyway. We Oh
my
>> Oh my. [laughter]
>> All right, your turn. Go. Your turn.
>> No. No. My name's like, no.
>> This has got to come out. [laughter]
Oh, that feels like pretty good.
[laughter]
>> You've just filled the whole thing with
glass.
>> That Okay, at least we've got that out
of our system. Oh, one more.
[laughter]
>> Okay, we're definitely getting banned
from Bugatti.
>> Basically in a simulation. We're in a
simulation. Just lifted a basketball
court up to bring Bri out.
Just get any concepts on it.
>> Joe, there's two wing mirrors. How do
you only use one then? [laughter]
>> Oh my days.
>> Oh yeah, we're right on the corner of
the ramp. Yeah.
>> Okay.
The ramp came up.
>> Okay. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
>> Crashed already.
>> Well, we can fix [music] the wheel as
long as it's not magn
How bad is it? [laughter]
>> It's like a seven.
>> Seven.
>> Bit more to the left.
>> Oh, no. That's perfect.
>> Yeah, you
send.
>> Wait, wait, wait. No. Slowly. Perfect.
Perfect. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You see what $150,000 of headlights
looks like?
>> Yeah, that's crazy.
>> That's for you, my brother.
>> You can have that one. I'll keep this
one.
>> Fiber in the middle. The good thing is
the inside is pretty good.
>> Yeah, this this I don't know how we're
going to figure that out.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah, that we can fix that.
We've We've done worse.
>> Oh,
>> yeah. This one is a lot worse.
>> Okay.
>> I don't even know is that bad.
>> Okay. Yeah, that one is worse. Well, at
least we got one good one.
That's normally the thing that holds me
back. Like the only
>> This is sick.
This going like 200 mph must feel crazy.
>> Feels pretty cool. I'm not going to lie.
[laughter]
>> Yo, how does it feel from inside the
car?
>> It feels like I've crashed it.
>> Do you know like when you were a kid,
you used to like dream of like driving a
Bugatti? That was not how I expected it.
Airbags out and someone's legs hanging
out over the rear view camera.
[laughter]
This is it. This is where we're
rebuilding it. We're going to do it
right here. That's it. We're going to
start stripping it apart. Whether we
bugatti like it or not, we're going to
start it. Every single damaged part on
this car needs to be taken off. And then
we can work out how we're going to fix
it, what we're going to replace, what
we're going to fix. This is it. So,
Bugatti, if you're watching and if you'd
like to come on board with this rebuild,
now's the time. If not, we're going to
continue anyway.
Let's stop.
[laughter]
When you talked about fixing and
rebuilding, who's paying? [laughter]
>> Any money with me? So,
>> Oh, [laughter]
you ready?
>> Oh. A [laughter]
>> okay.
>> I would have not bought this car without
you. You You understand that, right?
[laughter]
>> Yeah. We've realized that. We've
realized that
>> you were I would have never even bought
this car back if you would not even
>> You realize that I've only met you once
as well and you trusted me.
>> Oh, that's all I needed.
>> Trust me. That's crazy.
>> The accent just made me trust you.
>> So, we've already gathered that you've
just completely ruined any relationship
with Bugatti. So, that's a a great place
to start. So, thanks for that. Anyway,
so what we've got to do now is try and
figure out how we're going to build it
without using Bugatti.
>> Yeah,
>> the car is a Bugatti, but it uses a lot
of Volkswagen parts.
>> How comfortable, like how fast do you
think it'll take you to strip the whole
thing apart?
>> Well, I've never worked on one before.
Um, but I think in this just tonight,
we'll get the majority of it stripped.
Anything that's damaged is coming off.
>> We're going to get anything anything
damaged coming off. And then we can work
out what we need to replace, what we
need to fix, what we need to make,
fabricate.
>> You need You need help? I think I could.
I think I could.
>> Yeah, we're going to need help.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We're [laughter]
>> That's what we're here for. We're here
to
>> reporting for duty.
>> On the way here was like, why why have
you bought this car back that you've
probably never picked a spanner up ever?
>> No. No. I mean, I've tried. I have made
an attempt. I've taken a tower off
before. It's about it. These hands
aren't just for [__] typing, you
know? So, [laughter]
um,
>> well, your job luckily for this is he's
just going to make the money and we're
going to take it off him and rebuild
this. That's that's literally your job.
>> Yeah, I hope so. Well, mate, good luck.
Should we wear gloves? You guys wear
gloves or
>> um,
>> is that like female like?
>> No, no, no, no. Gloves is gloves. What
we do? We normally like gloves cuz we're
on and off the camera as well, but
>> Okay,
>> I doesn't matter. We can do it.
>> Wear mask. No mask.
>> Apron?
>> No, no mask. No mask. We're just going
to go in full scent. Let's get it apart.
>> Okay. work out how to do it.
>> Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
>> What side is he tightening?
[screaming]
>> Dialed. [laughter]
>> Maybe this car is going to get built.
>> You [laughter] couldn't do that.
>> Wait, should I do the other one?
>> Yeah. Yeah. We want the whole wheel off.
>> Oh, yeah.
built out but
>> Oh, this [__] weighs nothing.
>> What the hell? We just picked that up
with one hand.
>> No way.
>> Is it that light?
>> Yeah, it's pretty light.
>> Look at these things.
>> Oh my days. Like that is a huge break.
>> Light work.
>> [laughter]
>> You ever got that toy as a kid?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> It's pretty crazy. I've never worked on
a car.
>> First car I work on is a Bugatti.
>> That's crazy. [laughter]
>> I don't think many Bugatti owners
actually work on their own car. They
just give it to someone else to do,
which kind of what he's done. But And it
seems at the same time, at least he's
getting his hands dirty. Oh yeah,
>> he's going for it.
>> Oh yeah.
>> How long did you work at Dunkin Donuts
for?
>> I worked at Dunkin Donuts for about a
year and a half. I I worked at Crocs. I
worked at Aerapostal and then I worked
at Dunkin Donuts and then there I quit.
>> And then after Dunkin Donuts is that
>> that that's when like I made it,
[laughter]
you know.
>> Well, actually I Oh, I did made it, you
know. I made it out of Dunkin Donuts.
When I left Dunkin Donuts, I was making
like 5 6,000 a month. Oh, that's
>> it was like the same for me when I left
my job. It was like that's about enough
where I was like, "Yeah, I should quit
now."
>> Okay.
>> What's screwing? Nothing. [laughter]
>> Oh [__]
>> You missed one. Oh, [laughter]
>> isn't it true like the the more screws
you end up less [music] after you finish
fixing it, the better, right?
>> Yeah. And if you end up with any screw
left, each screw is 50 push-ups.
>> Ooh. So, that means you did a good job.
I think it Oh, look. It broke up here.
>> Oh, that'll go again.
>> That's fine, right?
>> That might be like five grand from
Bugatti. So, we should just use that
again.
>> Not happen. [laughter] We're not paying.
>> Have you been to England?
>> Yeah. I [__] hate it, man.
Where did you go?
>> I went to London. I've gone to
>> I've gone to London three times.
>> Why?
>> We We have a big audience there for
trading.
>> And we've gone to like do do like
private events with students.
>> Yeah.
>> And bro, everybody says the same thing.
Everybody hates it, bro.
>> Yeah. London is not It's not the one.
[laughter]
>> My back doesn't hurt from sitting down
all day, but it already hurts [laughter]
being here, bro. Mhm.
>> All right. We're on the way. You want to
drive your right hand drive or you
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. It'll be better.
Converted right and drive.
>> All right. Where where we going?
>> Tub guy.
>> Guy.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We're going to see
Matt. [laughter]
>> It's past my bedtime.
>> I I got a long drive back home. Good
luck. You can call me if you need
anything. I will send it to Chachi PT
and see what it can help [laughter] me.
>> So,
>> I'll see you tomorrow.
>> Yeah, tomorrow. I'll be here tomorrow.
>> Yeah. Um, it would look a lot different
tomorrow.
>> I mean, brother, this is a lot this is a
lot faster than I thought. I thought you
guys would take longer to [__] do
this.
>> Well, this is very fast.
>> We'll get that.
>> All right,
>> we'll get that.
>> See you guys tomorrow.
>> See you.
>> All right, ladies and gentlemen, it is
currently the next day. No trades today
in the markets. It's 5:00 p.m. Matt said
he was going to be at the shop. Let's
call him real quick. Yo [laughter]
>> yo
>> yo, I I thought you went back to the UK
for a second. How is it?
>> I'm going. [laughter]
How? It can't be that bad.
>> It's so bad.
>> Is Is it Is it really that bad?
>> Look at the sweat on this seat. This is
hard car [laughter] to work on.
>> Well, why why why is it like it's it's
actually built properly.
>> It is. Yeah. It's built to never come
apart. It is literally built. If it's
crashed, it's done. I'm sweating. I'm
working here. Look, there's all these
bolts all over the floor.
>> Oh my god, dude. How do you know how to
put it? How do you know how to put it
back together?
[snorts]
>> We'll [laughter] find out when we get to
it. The steering wheel is looking good.
Okay. Okay. Not bad. Not bad.
>> Um the the the outside is looking
better.
>> Oh wow. You took off the the windshield
>> and the whole front.
>> Dude, that doesn't even look like a
Bugatti anymore, bro. Holy [__] bro.
You need uh you you need a helping hand.
>> Oh yeah. Yeah. Like the the one thing we
need right now is you to come and help.
That is it. We like we need we just need
you on the spanners cuz I reckon like
done in 10 minutes.
>> Yeah. All right. Bet. All right. All
right. We're on the way then. We'll head
out.
All day.
>> All right, we're on the way. All right,
see you soon. [laughter]
>> Get SVJ. I haven't driven to SVJ in like
two weeks. All right, Matt, we're on the
way.
>> Who's that [__] Who's calling that
[__] Who's [music] that [__] Who's
that [__]
[music]
Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
>> Where the [__] the function? Where the
[__] the function? The way I feel right
now, I feel like we need to be.
>> Have you come to hell?
>> I came to help.
>> Thank you so much. We really need it.
[laughter]
>> You guys got
>> Yeah. Yeah, we got guns.
>> What's up, mate? [laughter]
>> What are you What are you doing down
there, man?
>> I'm losing my mind. [laughter]
>> This car is chaos.
>> Yeah. Yeah, this is Oh my god. Is
>> Is this the hardest build you've ever
done?
>> Yeah, like because we can't Google
anything. We found some interesting
things out though.
>> Is it is it
>> Well, we found ways to like save a lot
of money, but we're going to charge you
like obviously Bugatti prices.
>> No, just for the knowledge of finding
out. So,
>> the interesting Let me show you this.
So, this airbag, this is the one thing I
was worried about the whole time. That
with the Bugatti logo on, I thought,
"Okay, we're never going to get that." I
was like, "How are we going to get
that?" guy down the road, Matt at E3
Customs. I called him, he was like, "Oh,
we can repair this easily." Okay. So,
that's that repaired. Okay.
>> But then you need this to go inside.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Which is should be Bugatti,
right?
>> Yeah. Yeah. It should be Bugatti. But
this part number like which is really
just It was just on there bubbled up.
This is out of a Aston Martin DB11.
>> No way.
>> Yeah. Aston Martin DB at £1,800.
So to you £18,000. So [laughter]
Looks like a finder sp. We've got a
driver's airbag. Perfectly. Perfect.
Okay. The next thing we found
>> Uhhuh.
>> Okay.
>> Wait. This is the
>> This is the knee airbag. So, this is one
which you would have felt on your knees.
>> [__] up my knee right here.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So, this one, right?
Okay. This one Okay. We thought it was
special cuz it's got Bugatti.
>> Bugatti on it. Yeah. Yeah.
>> The craziest thing about this is that it
was this is minimum effort by Bugatti
because there's no other part numbers in
here. We tried every part number to try
and find everything, but Brietti part
number starts in 54B. It's at 5B4880841.
Okay, so that doesn't come up with
anything, but if you just take out the
5B4 and just put in the 880841C,
it comes up with an exact Audi A3 knee
airbag, which is £50, and it's exactly
the same.
>> Wait, but like like the the layout is
>> it's the same. Exactly the same. Matt
reacing [laughter]
the air, bro.
>> Literally £50 secondhand. $7.
>> $70. So, the airbags, we seem to have it
covered. We just want to get the the
dashboard airbag out. But the way it's
going so far, we're looking good for the
interior.
>> How much are we charging them for that?
>> Like I think we said 50 grand.
[laughter]
>> It takes rain power.
>> Okay. So driver airbag is
>> Aston Martin £1,800 that was from Aston
Martin and DB11.
>> This is Audi.
>> Yeah, this is Audi.
>> So what if like the one in the dash is
like Volkswagen?
>> It's going to be something European like
something European. Like we thought it
was all going to be like Volkswagen
Audi. But then when we seen the Aston
Martin airbag, we was like, what is that
doing in there? But they all must just
share the same company to get the
airbag. So that's pretty cool. We're
doing pretty good on the actual inside
of the car. On the outside of the car,
we we
>> [laughter]
>> this part. We can solve this. We've got
Spanish Bob. We called him. I don't know
if he is Spanish, but
>> he's Mexican. Yeah, Mexican.
>> Okay. Mexican Bob. We've got an Irish
Bob at home. So, like, yeah, we got a
Mex We got a Mexican Bob here. He's
going to copy that. Make that on there.
That's not a problem. He's going to make
that part. That's not a problem. We're
going to fix all the radiators. That's
not a problem.
>> Oh [__] the radiator.
>> Yeah. Oh, yeah. There was a lot of uh
you've got
>> Oh,
>> that's some serious damage to the
radiator,
>> bro. Bro, no wonder it was leaking,
dude. No,
>> there was no coolant left in this car.
>> Oh my god.
>> There was no You've got damaged radiator
there. You've got damaged radiator
there. You've got a damaged AC condenser
there. There was only one which
survived, which was on the front right.
>> Wow.
>> So, there was no coolant in this car.
>> Wait, so we we could repair these?
>> Yeah, these could be repaired or or
remade, which is fine. the headlights.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. [laughter]
One we think is repairable, but there is
a guy, right? There's a there's a guy
online who's got a set of those
headlights, but at the minute he wants
$150,000
for them. Like, [laughter]
>> [__] that guy.
[clears throat]
>> We might be able to get them for
cheaper. Also, he does have a complete
front end, but it's of a super sport. We
might be able to get the super sport
front end and then make Yeah. And then
make the put the vent in the panels and
everything like that, but that's
expensive. It was It was expensive. And
it How much did he want for
>> Well, at the minute, $550,000.
>> Was that with the headlights? Yeah.
>> 550,000. [laughter]
>> I didn't I didn't budget this.
>> Get your phone out. Get on [laughter] to
trading now.
[__] bro. [__]
>> I haven't I haven't checked it in like
two weeks, bro. I'm like [laughter]
>> That's the challenge.
>> One headlight is pretty bad.
>> You don't think it's repairable at all?
>> It might. It might be, but I don't think
it's ever going to go back to like look
right.
>> It would be easier for you to make 150
grand.
>> Yeah, [laughter]
>> but I think it's going to come down cuz
he keeps saying like, "Make me an offer.
Make me an offer."
>> So,
>> we can offer five grand, six grand,
[laughter]
>> depending what you want to do with the
car at the end. Um it depending what I I
don't mind like if we if it comes to it
I don't mind getting them and getting
the front end like out of my money
>> like like if you want to keep the car.
>> Yeah. And then like obviously you give
me a good price for the car at the end.
[laughter]
>> So
>> we can work that out.
>> But like I you can Yeah. We can I'm sure
we like you can drive it for a bit.
[laughter]
>> We shouldn't have said that about the
past.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I I thought,
well, Alex is probably going to want to
drive and everything at the end, but I I
will just ignore any video that goes out
of [laughter] the drive. We're looking
good so far. We want to know what you
want to do with the interior and how far
you want to go.
>> I definitely think the car should stay
purple, right? Like that's like the Even
though this is not the original color.
>> I I like the purple.
>> This is like the identity of the car,
you know? I think the interior should
match the purple.
>> Yeah.
>> I I was thinking like a white seat,
purple seat, black, purple, purple,
white. I don't know, you know? I don't I
don't know. What do you think? I'm open
to creativity. Like this bronze to me it
could go, you know. I'm not.
>> If we change all the bronze, what color
would you think would go with that?
>> Purple. [laughter]
>> I have a couple renders you want to see.
>> W Oh, yeah. Yeah. That's sick.
>> That's hot, right?
>> Yeah. That's sick.
>> Is that Louis Vuitton style like
designing? That looks cool.
>> Yeah. You see how like one seat is white
and purple? White and purple and white
and purple.
>> Oh, yeah. It's just got like a flip.
Yeah.
>> Yeah. You know, uh that's like the
original idea. Then they kind of we
changed the exposed to forged.
>> I don't know. It's only here.
>> So yeah, I think we take the whole I I
think it's worth doing because it
completely changed the car.
>> Yeah, I think it's worth doing.
>> You started. [laughter]
>> I think next time we come back, we want
to put the all the interior in, all the
airbags in and fix all this structure on
the front and put the radiators in. And
then it's after that
>> just reass body panels, headlights and
sort
the gearbox issue out as well. And then
that that's literally should be it. It's
not that bad.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
>> It's not that bad. [laughter]
>> Yeah. I think I'm excited for it. I'm
excited.
>> Okay. So, you generally do you want it.
Okay.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
Do you know like when I work on a car, I
get such an attachment to it.
>> Just don't crush it again.
>> Just don't crush it. Yeah. [laughter]
>> Just don't crush it. But
>> no promises. They're never ever going to
sell me a car. I'm never going to get an
application. I've accepted it.
>> No, that's fine. We just keep buying
them crashed.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. It's not a problem. It's not a
problem [laughter] at all. Just buy them
secondhand.
>> Now I got to wait for someone to crash
the turbion, though. I really want a
turbion.
>> I'm sure we can sort that out. Someone's
going to crash on.
>> Someone's going to [__] up.
>> I think Matt Matt is driving one at the
minute in the snow in
[laughter] [__] up.
>> [__] up.
>> Alex, you ready for your first job?
>> Yeah, I'm ready. That seat needs to come
out.
>> Okay.
>> I I need the gloves.
>> Put in
work.
>> Put him in that.
[laughter]
>> They're safety safety hazard, guys. You
know,
>> you never know when a screw is going to
go into your face,
>> brother. Now we talking.
No. [__] Wrong way.
Oh, yeah.
Bang.
>> Yeah.
>> Come on.
>> Good work. Good work. [laughter]
>> He's sweating.
>> Good work.
>> I'm done. That's it.
>> No. No. You got to take this interior
off now.
>> No. No. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done.
[laughter]
>> You can't be done.
>> If he breaks it, I'm going to have to
fix it. If he's [laughter]
>> he's done that.
>> He took one seat out and he's leaving.
>> He did a wheel yesterday and a seat
today. It's good progress, though. Now,
when it comes to putting the car back
together, at least he knows how the seat
goes in, how the wheels go on.
>> I'll take care of that. All right. Well,
hey, man. Hey, it's good meeting you.
[laughter]
>> No, it's a lovehate relationship with
this car. I feel like every single time
we drive it, I have to fill it up. All
it's good for is making noise and
shooting fins. We We got to show them
how we shoot flames. Let's show them.
Let's show them.
[music]
[singing]
>> And we're back, ladies and gentlemen, to
officially see how Matt Armstrong has
left the Bugatti. So, I this is actually
my first time walking up to it since
it's fully stripped out. Let's check it
out.
>> And it looks like a mess.
>> And it looks all [__] up. Oh, [__]
Yo, there really is carbon fiber
everywhere, bro. Holy [__] I can get
inside, right?
>> Last thing we need is the door to fall
off.
>> No, it should have fell off. Imagine.
>> Why did they leave the steering wheel,
bro? So, we're doing the whole interior
purple. They got to do the steering
wheel as well. Oh, we got to change
these buttons, bro. We get to change
these buttons to purple, too. Engine
purple. We'll change this to purple. Why
does it say do not turn?
>> Probably because they want us to turn
it.
>> Well, it's pretty crazy seeing a Bugatti
stripped down like this. I would never
expect in a million years. One, that I
would own a Bugatti at 25 years old. And
two, that I would have it fully stripped
down like this. Like, this is the
craziest [__] ever. This doesn't even
make sense to me. Like, bro,
>> we're probably the only people in the
world to be stripping this the way that
it's been stripped. I don't think
anybody has sat in a Bugatti Sharon
Pierce Sport like how I'm sitting in one
right now because I've seen other
Bugatti owners, no hate against them,
but dude, they treat the car like if it
was a like something delicate. Like, oh,
go in with certain shoes. Don't put your
feet on the like don't put your feet
here. Like, don't do this. Don't don't
like, you know, it's like, dude, it's a
[__] car at the end of the day.
>> Yeah. Hey, [snorts] $6 million car.
>> That's fine. These cars are meant to be
driven. They're meant to be built.
That's what they're meant for. They're
not meant to just look at them. I think
it's the biggest waste. Wo, can we lower
the miles now? Is there something that
we could do in here to lower [music] the
miles now?
>> Or is that is that fraud? Like,
>> brother, we were going good like
avoiding a lawsuit. Now you want to talk
about rolling back the miles on a
Bugatti.
>> Okay. Did you Did you notice? You know,
if you drive in reverse, the miles
actually go down. Since the car is
already this much disassembled, we can
just move this to here and then that's
it. This has to come in purple, too.
This feels as clunky as it sounds. All
right, let's get out of here. Well,
there's no door handle. Oh, wait, bro.
Wait, this is just like the Hondas, bro.
Wait, if I pull this, does the door
open? Look, I'm trying to I'm trying to
There's no way.
So, as of right now, what I do know is
that all the interior is being worked on
as we speak right now. Matt Armstrong
sent it to somebody. Yeah. So, I mean,
we're working to see what guys are going
to potentially 3D print some parts. What
parts we can somehow outsource and
figure out.
>> You saw what Matt Rimax said about 3D
printing the parts.
>> I I saw Matt Rimax reply and you know,
I'm going to go on a rant right now.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You know what, Matt
Matt Rimac, this is the message to you.
Don't take this personal. This is simply
my response to your safety argument
directly. First of all, I I want to let
you know that I agree entirely with your
safety standpoint. that safety is a very
big and important factor of having such
a powerful vehicle. A vehicle that has
15,600 horsepower, goes 225 mph. I agree
100%. I got into an accident with this
vehicle with my camera guy. And thanks
to the safety precautions that were
manufactured into this vehicle, it kept
us safe and we're here to tell the story
because of that. Airbags worked great.
Brakes were spectacular. The brakes
actually decelerate the car faster than
the car accelerates or that's what it
feels like. um the airbags, the seat,
everything worked great and because of
the safety, we're here to tell the
story. So, I agree with you. Safety is
the importance and the backbone of this
build. Now, my problem with your
response as to why you can't sell us
parts because it's a safety precaution.
I just believe it's inaccurate and not
true. I just believe you're trying to
control the situation. You not selling
us parts is forcing us to find
third-party solutions to make this car
get back on the road. you're forcing us
to figure this [__] out on a different
way because you're not giving us access
to the OEM parts. So, you're actually
putting us at more risk by not selling
us parts. And the truth of the fact is
that we will fix this car one way or
another. And what gets me even more
rattled is that we spoke on the phone.
When when we spoke on the phone, as soon
as I bought the car, I basically posted
on Instagram. I'm like, "Hey, Bugatti,
you got 24 hours to reply, or if not,
I'm going to 3D print the parts."
Obviously, it was a little bit of a
troll, but you replied within that
24-hour time span, and I respect that.
Such a highleveled CEO of yourself, a
billion dollar industry, a billion
dollar car brand. Replying to an
Instagram post of a 25-year-old shows
the care that you have for the brand. We
fast forward a couple of hours. We get
on the phone and you told me two things
on the phone. You told me the first
thing was that you're trying to figure
out how you can get us parts to this
vehicle and how you can help us rebuild
the car. or two that you would get a
technician out here to walk through with
us how this car is going to properly get
built. Do it to the Bugatti standard.
I'm not sure what happened. You gave me
your word on those two things. Not sure
what happened 24 hours later. Both those
things kind of went out the window. I'm
very big on my word. I think that moment
said a lot. Your whole end goal is
because of safety. Well, if there's a
big safety issue with this vehicle, when
your Bugatti inspector flew from France
to Miami when the insurance requested it
to see the actual damage of the vehicle
outside of the insurance technicians,
they could have labeled this car
certificate of destruction. They could
have labeled this car as no longer safe
and it cannot be back on the road. But
your Bugatti technician [music] did not
do that. They labeled this car as
salvage. this car is repairable and this
car will get rebuilt and it will be
inspected and be back on the road as a
rebuilt title. So, if there's a big
safety issue and the car is actually
that bad, they would have never let it
back on the road in the first place. So,
you're kind of leaving us with no choice
here to figure this out. And it it
really does suck. I I wish I can have
the cooperation of yourself, which
personally I I look up to you, Matt. You
know, I'm 25 years old. This is not my
first Bugatti. This is my second
Bugatti. I plan to continue to extend my
car collection over the next 15 20 years
and you will also be in the car industry
for the next 15 to 20 years. We will
bump into each other eventually and I
hope that we can work on something
together. Maybe I can get an allocation
on the turbion and see the build that
you're actually building yourself
because you claim that you didn't work
on the Chiron. So, I personally disagree
with your statement. I think that it's a
the wrong stance and you're actually
endangering us even more by not selling
us parts. All I can say is set and
forget. This build will continue one way
or another. I'm going to get my guy Juan
in Halia to uh just figure this [__] out
alongside with Matt Armstrong and we
will get this [__] back on the road.
>> Matt Armstrong said some [__] like
something with the gearbox was [__]
up.
>> He kind of showed it.
>> Did he say that we have to drop the
engine on this? Uh he said we might have
to.
It's
>> kind of the only way.
>> Should we?
>> You know, it's fine. We're in Miami,
bro. We're We're basically in the middle
of high. We could just get two forklifts
and just like pull it apart.
>> Should we put an exhaust on it when we
take out the engine?
>> I think we should put an exhaust
intakes, down pipes,
>> two E brake.
[music]
Hey, I'm on that [__] Hey, murder
[music] gang [__] Ain't slow to [__] A
murder gang [__]
>> All right, so I got this gift from Matt
Armstrong. This is for Matt himself. He
has a long flight back home. If he's
able to rebuild my Bugatti, he's going
to be able to build this one on the
flight. And this is for his filmer. Cool
guy. Loves Porsches. So, we're going to
give him this now. [laughter]
>> It's just a gift. It's a It's a It's a
motivational gift.
>> This is [laughter]
And this is for you. Oh, look at that.
I'm pleased with that.
>> Yeah, that's sick.
>> My process is like, if you could fix
this, you could fix this.
>> I think we can learn how to do it on
this. I'll do this on the plane on the
way home.
>> Yeah, exactly. There you go. [laughter]
>> Thank you. That's sick.
>> Thank you.
>> So, we can have a race after.
>> Yeah. Well, we can race to build it. How
many pieces you got?
>> Uh, 348.
>> I got 771.
>> Oh,
>> bit harder for me.
>> Yeah, but you're a mechanic, so you got
an advantage. We got to get used to
building these Bugattis if we want to
get like a certified Bugatti certificate
from